賓州代表- 彼得魯索
不好意思，我是保羅卡普拉  我來找克裏絲汀娜
Hey, excuse me. I'm Paul Capra.  I'm here to see Christina.
這邊請，卡普拉先生  她在等你
Right this way, Mr. Capra,  she's expecting you.
- 保羅  - 克裏絲汀娜
-Paul.  -Hey, Christina.
你好
Hi.
- 見到你真好  - 我也是
-It's good to see you.  -Yeah, you too.
要吃什麼嗎？
Can I get you anything?
我在來的路上吃過早餐了
No, I grabbed some breakfast  on the way down.
請坐
Okay, have a seat.
我和民主黨國會競選委員會  和全委會談過
I asked you down here  because I spoke to D-trip and the DNC.
我們希望你競選彼得的席位
We'd like you to run for Peter's seat.
你應該知道  選舉是在二月第一周
As you probably know, the election  has been set for the first week of February.
你要我參選？
You want me to run?
以你的社區聲望  和基層組織經驗…
With your stature in the community,  your grass-roots organizing experience...
克裏絲汀娜，等等…
Christina, hold on...
我知道有很多需要考慮
I know it's a lot to consider.
才過了一個月
It's only been a month.
我們還是需要議員，保羅
We still have to govern, Paul.
我以為你找我來  是想要跟我談什麼事
I thought you asked me down here  because you wanted to talk or something.
我是想跟你談選舉
I do, about the election.
我是指彼得
I mean about Peter.
你怎麼沒去葬禮？
How come you didn't go to the funeral?
我做不到
I couldn't.
- 你還好嗎？  - 我沒事
-How you been holding up?  -I'm all right.
- 讓辦公室正常運轉很辛苦  - 天啊，別管辦公室
-It's been hard keeping the office on track.  -Jesus. Screw the office.
你自己呢？
What about you?
你有權難過，克裏絲汀娜
You're allowed to grieve, Christina.
保羅
Paul,
有60萬人仰賴著我們
there are 600,000 people counting on us.
我不能感情用事
I can't let my feelings get in the way of that.
你願意聽我說完  競選彼得席位的事嗎？
Will you hear me out  about running for Peter's seat?
你的審查通過了，非常出色
Well, you've passed the vetting process  with flying colors.
- 有沒有遺漏的地方？  - 沒有，長官
-ls there anything we might have missed?  -No, sir.
跟我說說監督改革委員會  主席的經歷
Tell me about your experience as the Chair  of the Oversight and Reform Committee.
非常有收穫
It's been very rewarding.
你面臨過最大的挑戰是什麼？
What are the biggest challenges  you've had to face?
黨派偏見
Partisanship.
435個自大狂擠在一起
Well, I suppose a room filled  with 435 big egos
對監督改革委員會來說  的確不是什麼舒服的事
isn't the most hospitable place for oversight.
塔碧莎，你想當副總統嗎？
Do you want to be Vice President, Tabitha?
那是我莫大的榮幸，長官
It would be a great honor, sir.
我們保持連繫
We'll be in touch.
- 就這樣？  - 暫時就這樣
-That's all?  -For the time being.
謝謝，總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
- 我們不能用她  - 同意
-We have to cross her off.  -I agree.
毒蟲聽她說話都會睡著
She could put a crack addict to sleep.
那她怎麼會出現在名單上？
Then what is she doing on the goddamn list?
塔碧莎是很聰明的議員
Tabitha's a very gifted legislator.
我不要履歷看起來不錯的人
I don't want people  who make sense on paper.
我要至少一個可行的人選
I need at least one viable option.
你們提名的名單
The two of you've created this list,
然後劃掉上面每一個名字
and have proceeded to cross off  every name you've put on it.
這只是第一步
It's just a first pass, sir.
我們需要時間去…
We need time to fully vet all...
吉姆會奪下賓州
Jim is going to win this thing  in Pennsylvania.
一個月來替補人選的進展  毫無成果
And we're no closer to naming  his replacement than we were a month ago.
再給我們一點時間  我們會多給你幾個名字考慮
Let us take another crack at it,  and give you a few more names to consider.
只要一個名字就夠了
I just want one name.
明早會準備好
We'll have something for you  by tomorrow morning.
謝謝，總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
他已經準備好同意任何事了
He's ready to say yes to anything.
為了成功，第一次提名時
Yeah, for this to work,  I don't think you can be there.
- 你別在場  - 同意
-Not when I first mention it.  -I agree.
你在晨報時提出  我到時，會露出驚訝樣
You bring it up in your morning brief  and when I show up, I'll act surprised.
如果他願意接受的話
Assuming he's open to the idea.
明天只要把這想法  灌輸給他就好
Look, all we have to do tomorrow is plant  the notion in his head.
我相信你會很有說服力
I'm sure you'll be persuasive.
喂？
Hello?
- 卡普拉先生？  - 我是，你哪位？
-Mr. Capra?  -Yeah. Who's this?
我是《頭條報導》的  珍妮史柯斯基
Janine Skorsky from Slugline.
我寫魯索議員去世新聞時  跟你談過
We spoke when I wrote the piece  about Congressman Russo's passing.
我不想再接受  關於彼得的訪問了
I'm done giving interviews  about Peter, okay?
他是個麻煩人物，就這樣
He was a troubled guy, end of story.
我不是想談這個
This is not about his death.
我打給你是因為  我的國會競選委員會線人告訴我
I'm calling you because my sources  at the DCCC are telling me
你也許會競選他的席位
that you might be running for his seat.
我不想談這個
I'm not talking about that.
但你今早和克裏絲汀娜葛蘭格  見過面吧？
But you did have a meeting this morning  with Christina Gallagher, correct?
我在開車，不能講電話
I'm driving right now.  I really shouldn't be on the phone.
如果你要參選
If you do run,
我想瞭解你在費城造船廠  關閉事件扮演的角色
I would like to know about your involvement  in the closing of the Philadelphia Shipyard.
那是華府做的決定  沒有詢問過工業會
That decision was made in Washington.  The Association wasn't consulted.
抱歉，我不太相信
Forgive me, I find that hard to believe.
我讀了所有基地重組  與關閉委員會的紀錄
I read all of the transcripts  from the BRAC Commission.
魯索議員沒有任何證詞
Congressman Russo  didn't give any testimony.
你說他連一次  都沒有徵求過你的意見…
So are you saying that he didn't consult  with you once before he...
有人對他施壓，這就是政治
Somebody was strong-arming him, okay?  It was politics.
你知道有誰會對他施壓嗎？
Do you know who would have  pressured him?
我不知道  他只說是食物鏈的上層
I don't know.  He just said people up the food chain.
他有沒有說過任何具體的…
Did he say anything more specific about...
路上塞車，我得掛了
You know what? There's traffic. I gotta go.
卡普拉先生，我想…
Mr. Capra, I would love to...
我該準備通知媒體了嗎？
Should I be prepared to do press?
如果他願意的話
If he's amenable.
你覺得機會有多大？
What do you think our chances are?
我覺得有一半以上
Better than 50-50, if I had to say.
不過要等馬修贏了之後  才會宣佈
We won't announce until after  Matthews wins, though.
我不想承認，我很緊張…
I hate to admit it, but I'm nervous...
我也是
So am l.
- 因為上一次我們發現…  - 這也是我的擔心
-It's just that last time we found ourselves...  -That's my fear, too.
無論結果如何  都要打電話跟我說
All right. You call me, either way?
九小時內就會知道了
In no more than nine hours.
琳達在裏面太久了
Linda's been in there far too long.
如果要用這麼久來說服總統  就不是好預兆
If the President takes this much convincing,  it doesn't bode well.
我能感覺到  他在門那邊的猶豫
I can feel it, his hesitation,  on the other side of that door.
我瞭解擔心毫無意義  除非我知道手中握的牌
I know it's pointless to worry  until I know what cards I'm holding.
也許他只是被打斷…
Perhaps he just got interrupted by some...
他想要推選瑞蒙塔斯克
He wants to tap Raymond Tusk.
什麼？
What?
他認為這樣很大膽
He thinks it's a bold idea.
這樣很蠢
That's an idiotic idea.
他從來沒擔任過公職
The man's never held public office.
這也是總統說  他喜歡他的理由之一
That's one of the things  the President said he likes about him.
現在經濟不景氣  總統卻想提名億萬富翁？
The President wants to nominate  a multi-billionaire in a struggling economy?
他會失去半數選民
He'll alienate half the country.
我也是這麼對他說的
Which is exactly what I said to him,
但他明確表示  不想要我跟他爭這件事
but he made it very clear  he does not want me to fight him on this.
所以你根本沒提到我？
So you didn't mention me at all?
我根本沒機會
I never had the chance.
在我開口前，他就心意已決
His mind was made up  before I could say a word.
那我們就得讓他反悔
Well, we have to un-make it.
你可以試試看  可是你一旦這麼做
Well, you can try, but if you do,
我猜他就不會再讓你涉入了
my guess is he's gonna cut you out  of the process altogether.
他看起來很堅持
He seemed adamant.
我們該進去了
We should go in there.
- 總統先生  - 早安，法蘭
-Mr. President.  -Morning, Frank.
琳達，可以讓我們  單獨聊一下嗎？
Will you give us a few minutes, Linda?
當然
Of course.
琳達告訴你了？
Linda fill you in?
我認為瑞蒙塔斯克…
I think Raymond Tusk...
是一個令人激動的大膽決定
Is an exciting, bold idea.
我很高興你贊同  琳達不這麼想
Well, I'm glad you agree.  Linda didn't think so.
他是見過世面的生意人  聰明卻腳踏實地
He's a proven businessman,  brilliant but down-to-earth.
- 你認識他嗎？  - 我在募款會跟他見過面
-Do you know him personally?  -I met him briefly once at a fundraiser.
昨晚打給他時
Last night when I called him was
是我們第一次有實質交談
the first time we had  a meaningful conversation.
他願意嗎？
Did he seem open to the idea?
我覺得他有點不情願
I sensed a good deal of reluctance.
他想要幾天時間來考慮
He wanted a few days to consider.
很好，剛好給我們時間做審查
Well, good, that gives us time  to start vetting him.
他沒問題
He's clean.
去年我就對他做過調查了
I had him vetted last year
我當時考慮讓他擔任財政部長
when I was considering him  for Secretary of the Treasury.
他有說為什麼不情願嗎？
And did he say why he's reluctant?
沒有，只說想考慮一下
No, didn't give a reason.  Just wanted to mull it over.
我想派人去聖路易  當面和他聊聊
I want to send someone to St. Louis  to speak to him in person,
說服他接受提名
convince him to accept the nomination.
你想派誰去？
Who are you thinking about?
我想派琳達  但她這裏的工作太多
I'd send Linda, but there's so much work  for her to do here.
她有時不太友善
And she can be abrasive at times.
她有時很難相處
Yeah, she can be a bit tough.
我想找個嚴肅的人
I want someone with gravitas.
柏許是個人選  但他不是我們的死忠盟友
Birch is a possibility,  but he's not always been our strongest ally.
我不會把這種事情交給鮑伯
I'm not sure I would trust Bob  with something like this.
我願意親自前往，長官
I would be happy to go myself, sir.
我可以適度地刺激他  給他應得的尊重
I can use a light touch,  and give him the respect he deserves.
好，我會通知他的人  說你會過去
Good. I'll let his people know you're coming.
- 謝謝，總統先生  - 謝謝，法蘭
-Thank you, Mr. President.  -Thank you, Frank.
說吧，法蘭斯
Tell me, Francis.
還好我們做了萬全準備  我今晚得飛去聖路易
It's good we were prepared for anything.  I have to fly to St. Louis tonight.
「有人對他施壓」  當我問他是誰時
"Somebody was strong-arming him."  And when I asked him who,
他說是食物鏈的上層
he said, quote, people up the food chain.
那是華府
It's Washington.
議員們總是會被施壓
Congressmen get strong-armed all the time.
我直覺是法蘭安德沃
My gut says it was Frank Underwood.
在造船廠關閉前  他和魯索毫無交集
He had nothing to do with Russo  before the shipyard closing,
- 然後突然跳出來支持他…  - 那不代表…
-and then suddenly he's propping him up...  -That doesn't mean he was...
別繼續胡扯了，喬伊
Let's cut the bullshit once and for all, Zoe.
我知道你的故事都是他提供的
I know he's been feeding you your stories.
我不想害你  但我也不會停止調查這件事
I don't want to screw you over,  but I'm not going to stop digging on this.
他不是我的線人
I won't say he was a source.
但你們的確認識
But you do know each other.
給我看你的筆記  我去找他談
Show me your notes and I'll talk to him.
這是和卡普拉通話的筆記
These are the notes from the Capra call.
這些是基地重組  與關閉委員會的紀錄
And these are the transcripts from  the BRAC hearing.
當他們提到費城造船廠時  魯索什麼都沒說
When they get to the Philadelphia Shipyard,  Russo doesn't say anything.
沒關係
That's fine.
我會把兩個都放在檔案裏
Yeah, I would just put both of them  in that file.
克萊兒，我剛接到  善可工業公關部的電話
Claire, I just got a call from  the PR office at SanCorp
說他們要派攝影小組過來
saying they wanted to send a film crew
拍攝我們在波札納的  過濾計劃
to take footage  of our filtration project in Botswana.
對，他們要用來做宣傳
Right. They're just using that  for promotional material.
善可工業在分水嶺提案  反對我們
SanCorp fought us on the Watershed Bill.
他們幫我們  從南蘇丹把過濾器運出來
They helped us get the filters  out of South Sudan.
我以為是國務院
I thought that was the State Department.
不是，你記得瑞米丹頓嗎？
No. You remember Remy Danton?
你剛進來的時候  在你的辦公室裏見過他？
You met him in your office  right after you started working here?
- 那個說客  - 我請他幫過忙
-The lobbyist.  -I asked him for his help.
我們只是還人情，僅此而已
We're just returning the favor. That's all.
克萊兒，他們反對  所有我們支持的東西
Claire, they're against  everything we stand for.
這完全無害
It's harmless.
他們會把影片  傳給幾個投資者
They'll send the video  to a few of their investors,
做些廣告
and make some commercials.
這讓我感覺非常不舒服  這個主意…
This makes me very uncomfortable.  The idea...
攝影小組已經出發了，吉莉安  請你和他們合作
They are sending the film crew, Gillian.  So please work with them on that.
我有個同事在調查彼得魯索
One of my colleagues  is looking into Peter Russo.
她覺得是你在背後  逼他關閉造船廠
The assumption is you strong-armed  him into closing the shipyard.
你同事的消息是從哪來的？
Where does your colleague  get their information?
我不知道
I don't know.
任何人都可以  對國防部的預算分配發表意見
Allocating the DoD budget  is always a free-for-all.
你有對他施壓嗎？
Did you pressure him?
基地提早關閉
There were certain people  that were gonna benefit
會讓有些人從中獲益
from the base closing sooner  rather than later.
我沒有對彼得施壓
I didn't strong-arm Peter,
我建議他從失敗轉為勝利
I advised him to trade in a losing hand  for a winning one.
靠什麼？
How did he stand to win?
他從敵人中爭取同伴  這在國會裏是非常有價值的
He made allies out of enemies.  That's a very valuable thing in Congress.
我希望能給你更多爆料
I wish I could give you something juicier,
但關閉造船廠  只是普通的政治活動
but the shipyard closing  was just politics as usual.
我猜你的那位同事  是史柯斯基小姐
I assume your colleague is Ms. Skorsky.
- 她知道我們有接觸嗎？  - 當然沒有
-She know we're talking?  -No, of course not.
保持連絡
Be in touch.
瑞蒙亞倫塔斯克的資料  比你想要的還多
More than you ever wanted to know  about Raymond Alan Tusk.
他名下的公司、政治獻金
Companies he controls,  political contributions,
雜誌稱他為「荒野億萬富翁」  形容他樸實的中西部生活方式
a GQ article entitled "Backwoods Billionaire"  is about his humble mid-western lifestyle.
天啊
Jesus.
還有財務揭露規定
There's also a copy  of the financial disclosure requirements
跟盲目信託的復本
and details of the blind trust.
你要特別注意這個信託
I think the trust is where you want to focus.
- 幕後黑手會不會是琳達？  - 有什麼目的？
-Could Linda be behind all this?  -To what end?
為了讓你離開幾天
To get you out of town for a few days
好讓他們不受你干擾  繼續搜尋
while they continue the search  without your interference?
總統沒理由不信任我
The President has no reason to mistrust me.
除非琳達跟他說  你想要當副總統
Unless Linda told him  you want the Vice Presidency.
不會，她陷得太深了
No, she's in way too deep.
在國務卿提名時  我們誤判過她…
We misjudged her on  the Secretary of State nomination...
那次不一樣
That was different.
她當時是攻其不備  現在她知道我隨時保持警覺
She blindsided me.  Now she knows my eyes are wide open.
你要帶運動包  還是一般公事包？
Do you want the Gaffney bag  or regular business?
一般公事包
Regular business.
塔斯克穿著簡樸是他的自由  但我代表白宮
Tusk can dress down if he wants to,  but I'm representing the White House.
讓華特多爾去調查塔斯克  看能不能找出什麼秘密
And get Walter Doyle onto Tusk.  Let's see ifwe can dig up anything.
我馬上打給他
I'll call him right now.
我不在時  盯著珍妮史柯斯基
And keep your eye on Janine Skorsky  while I'm away.
她在調查魯索
She's been prying into Russo.
她知道什麼？
What does she know?
她知道該問什麼問題
She knows the right questions to ask.
我要確保  她得不到該知道的答案
I want to make sure  she doesn't get the right answers.
交給我
I'm on it.
麥卡汀
McCuddin.
- 你說什麼？  - 麥卡汀空軍基地
-What was that?  -McCuddin Air Force Base.
基地重組與關閉聽證會  是在4月12日舉行的
BRAC hearing was there on April 12.
接著大衛拉斯穆森  不到一周就下台
David Rasmussen stepped down  less than a week later.
- 沃麥克接棒，所以也許…  - 等等…說慢點
-Womack takes his place. So maybe...  -So wait... Slow down.
麥卡汀在他的選區
McCuddin is in his district.
是那個造船廠的事嗎？
Is that the shipyard thing?
珍妮，回電給我  我覺得是沃麥克對魯索施壓
Janine, call me back.  I think it was Womack who pressured Russo.
魯索大概是想讓他  欠自己一個人情
Russo was probably just earning a favor  he could cash in later.
我等你電話
I'm around.
你曾為了要取消報導  跟她吵架嗎？
Did you ever have to fight her to kill a story?
- 珍妮嗎？  - 對，她為你工作的時候
-Janine?  -Yeah, when she worked for you.
只有在她錯的時候
Only when I knew she was wrong.
她想把整個陰謀論
She's trying to draw up  this whole conspiracy thing
跟魯索、法蘭安德沃  和造船廠關閉的事連在一起
with Russo and Frank Underwood  and the whole shipyard closing.
但我很確定她錯了
But I'm pretty sure she's wrong.
很確定不等於絕對
Pretty sure isn't the same as certain.
我絕對確定
No, I am certain.
- 怎麼知道？  - 我有線人
-How do you know?  -I have sources.
- 安德沃？  - 不是
-Underwood?  -No.
沒事，我會想出辦法
No, never mind. I'll figure it out.
- 塔斯剋夫人？  - 請叫我珍
-Mrs. Tusk?  -Jean, please.
你一定是法蘭，請進
You must be Frank. Come in.
很高興見到你
So nice to meet you.
客房在這裏
The guest room is this way.
謝謝你們邀請我住在這裏
It is very kind of you to have invited me  to stay here.
我家的床這麼舒服  何必要浪費納稅人的錢住旅館？
Why waste the taxpayers' money on a hotel  when we have a perfectly good bed?
我和他們都感激不盡
Well, both they and I are very grateful.
抱歉瑞蒙沒有招呼你  他已經睡了…
I'm sorry Raymond isn't awake  to greet you, he goes to bed at...
我知道他是早睡早起的人  我瞭解
I know, he's an early riser. I understand.
早上需要我敲門嗎？
Would you like a wake-up knock?
不用，我手機上有鬧鐘
No, I have an alarm on my phone.
- 好好休息  - 非常感謝
-Sleep tight.  -Thank you so much.
我想說早安，但現在是半夜
I would say good morning,  but it's the middle of the night.
- 很榮幸認識你  - 我也是
-It's a pleasure to meet you.  -And you, too.
- 我太大聲了嗎？  - 不，我聞到培根的香味
-Was I making too much noise?  -No, I smelled bacon.
來
Here.
咖啡？酒？  現在凌晨2點，兩種都行
Coffee? Booze?  2:00 a.m. you can go either way.
水就好
Just water for now.
這是過濾水  你老婆會同意你喝的
It's filtered. Your wife would approve.
你以前來過聖路易嗎？
You ever been to St. Louis before?
只去過機場
Just the airport.
目前為止，你覺得怎麼樣？
What do you think so far?
我只看到你家附近
Well, I've only seen your neighborhood
還有窗戶外面  州際公路旁的景色
and whatever I could see out the window  on the interstate.
夠了，走到哪都是這個樣子
Good enough. It's all pretty much the same.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我還沒洗澡
Listen, I still haven't showered.
我的心思還在中國
My mind is on China here.
你要不要再去休息一下
What do you say you get a few more z's
過幾小時  等我們穿好衣服再談？
and we try this again  in a few hours with our clothes on?
聽起來不錯
Sounds like a plan.
9點半在我辦公室見  我請司機來接你
Meet me at my office at 9:30.  I'll have a driver pick you up.
能請問你為什麼這麼做嗎？
Can I ask why you do that?
- 做什麼？  - 那樣敲戒指
-Do what?  -Tap your ring like that.
我在電視上也看過你這樣
I've seen you do it on TV.
當你離開桌子或講台時  都會敲兩下
Two taps every time you get up from a table  or leave a lectern.
是我父親教我的
Something my father taught me.
讓你的關節變硬  這樣打架時就不會受傷
It's meant to harden your knuckles so  you don't break them if you get into a fight.
敲木頭還會帶來好運
It also has the added benefit  of knocking on wood.
我父親堅信  成功需要準備加上運氣
My father believed that success  is a mixture of preparation and luck.
敲桌子是一箭雙鵰
Tapping the table kills both birds  with one stone.
你父親是桃農？
Your father was a peach farmer?
對，不怎麼成功就是了
Yes, he was.  Not a very successful one.
缺乏準備還是缺乏運氣？
Lack of preparation or lack of luck?
兩者都缺
Lack of both.
他比較擅長給建議  而不是照建議行事
He was better at giving advice  than following it.
小姐，你的卡
Miss, your card.
謝謝
Thank you.
葛蘭格小姐
Ms. Gallagher,
我叫珍妮史柯斯基  我是《頭條報導》的記者
my name's Janine Skorsky,  I'm a reporter at Slugline.
- 我是寫議員報導…  - 我記得
-I wrote the profile on Congressman...  -I remember.
你有空嗎？
Do you have a minute?
- 如果要談彼得，我…  - 不，是關於保羅卡普拉
-lf this is about Peter, l...  -No. It's about Paul Capra.
我們知道他也許  會競選魯索議員的空缺
We know that he might be running  for Congressman Russo's old seat.
我無可奉告
I can't comment on that.
我們只想調查  去年四月造船廠關閉的事
We're just trying to do some background  on the shipyard closing last April.
我只想吃早餐…
Listen, I just want to eat my breakfast...
我們有消息指出
We have sources that are saying
議員遭受施壓  才沒有對關閉表示反對
that the Congressman was being pressured  by someone to not fight the closure.
誰？
Who?
我也想搞清楚
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
這些都不會留下紀錄  我保證
This is completely off the record,  I promise you.
克裏絲汀娜
Hi, Christina.
道格，你好
Doug, hi.
- 你好嗎？  - 我很好
-How you holding up?  -I'm okay. I'm good.
- 我看到你坐在這裏，能坐下嗎？  - 沒問題
-I saw you sitting over here, you mind if l?  -No, please.
史柯斯基小姐吧？
Ms. Skorsky, right?
你在《先軀報》工作時  我們應該談過幾次話…
I believe we spoke a few times  when you used to work for The Herald...
每次我趁機穿過  媒體辦公室的重重火網時
Whenever I could get past  the press office gauntlet to you.
我們的確蠻嚴的
We do like to run a tight ship.
你來國會有什麼事？
So what brings you to the Capitol?
我在問葛蘭格小姐
I was just asking Ms. Gallagher
誰會參選賓州第一選區的空缺
who's running to fill the vacant seat  in Pennsylvania's 1st.
我們真的不知道
Well, the honest answer is we don't know.
謝謝你撥時間，葛蘭格小姐
Thank you for your time, Ms. Gallagher.
有人拿你不想回答的問題  來騷擾你，就告訴我一聲
Anyone starts harassing you with questions  you don't want to answer, you let me know.
我來對付他們
I'll handle them.
你已經有太多事要承擔
You got enough on your plate right now.
謝謝，道格，我很感激
Thanks, Doug. I appreciate that.
堅持住，好嗎？
Hang in there, okay?
好
Yes.
烏干達、秘魯
Uganda, Peru,
尼泊爾、印尼
Nepal, lndonesia,
尼加拉瓜
Nicaragua.
你真愛旅行
Well, you are quite the well-traveled man.
不，我只待在家裏  是珍帶回來給我的
No. I'm the man who stays at home.  Jean brought those back for me.
- 塔斯克先生，我…  - 叫名字就好
-Mr. Tusk, I am...  -First names.
畢竟我們一起吃過碎培根  可以安心假設我們很熟了
After all, we have broken bacon together,  we can safely assume that we're familiar.
瑞蒙，我知道你很忙
Raymond, I realize that  you are a very busy man,
所以我就開門見山說了
so I'm gonna cut right to the chase.
總統誠摯希望  你成為下屆副總統
The President sincerely would like you  to become the next Vice President.
這我已經知道了
That part I already knew.
我是來說服你同意的
And I'm here to convince you to say yes.
這我也已經知道了
Another thing I already knew.
我不知道能不能告訴你  你不知道的事
Well, I don't know that I can tell you  anything you don't already know.
但也許你能告訴我  你在猶豫什麼
But perhaps you can tell me  what your hesitation is.
說吧
Speak.
好
Yes.
我知道也許你會擔心
Now, I understand  you might have some concerns
財務揭露會導致…
about the financial disclosures leading...
說吧
Speak.
不好
No.
現在有八個人代表我
I have eight people representing me
在六個不同的時區  同時參加八個會議
at eight simultaneous meetings  in six time zones right now.
我坐在這裏回答他們的問題
I sit here and answer their questions,
他們用簡單的是非題問我
provided they come in the form  of a single yes or no proposition.
那讓我來試一下
Well, then let me give that a try.
你想當副總統嗎，是或否？
Would you like to be the Vice President,  yes or no?
等一下
Hold on a minute.
非常抱歉
I am very sorry.
給我20分鐘結束這些會議
Let me have 20 minutes  to wrap up these meetings.
然後我們離開辦公室
And then what do you say  we get out of the office
遠離這討厭的電話如何？
and away from this damn phone?
在我車裏等我  貝蒂會告訴你車停在哪裏
Meet me at my car.  Betty can tell you where it's parked.
說吧
Go ahead.
他開始動搖了
He's deflecting.
但我看不出來  他是因為想說否
What I can't tell is whether  it's because he's inclined to say no
還是想要我求他說是
or wants to be wooed to say yes.
無論如何我得讓他言歸正傳  不能太過唐突
Either way I'll have to ease him into  the conversation, not be so blunt.
這一趟旅行  可能會比我想像的還久
This trip may take longer than I thought.
我們查了所有檔案櫃
We've looked through all the file cabinets.
不在電腦裏嗎？
They're not on his computer?
議員的手寫筆記裏也沒有
Not with the Congressman's  handwritten notes.
好，我來找他的辦公室
All right. I'll check his office.
這片森林能讓人放鬆
There's a comfort to these woods,
就像我的後院一樣
Iike they're my backyard.
其實的確也算是我的後院  這在我名下
Well, they are my backyard in a way.  I own them.
- 面積多大？  - 六千英畝
-How much land?  -6,000 acres.
我既然來了，可以去參觀  你的富爾頓核電廠嗎？
You think I could get a tour  of your Fulton Plant while I'm in town?
如果你要的話
If you like,
但我不懂既然你能待在這裏  何必要去那裏
but I don't know why you'd want  to be there when you could be out here.
我從沒見過核電廠
I've never seen a nuclear plant.
沒什麼好看的
Not much to see.
鋼鐵、水泥、很多蒸汽
Steel, concrete, lot of steam.
總統一直都不太支持核能
The President hasn't exactly been  a big supporter of nuclear power.
這是你猶豫的原因之一  擔心總統府會…
Is that part of your hesitation,  that fear that the Administration...
這只是他的意識表現
He's just being savvy.
日本核災之後  就很難推廣核能了
Nuclear energy is a tough sell after Japan.
但這是目前唯一的選擇  才能避免徹底摧毀地球
But it's the only option we have right now  that doesn't completely trash the planet.
反對核能的言論  只是感情用事
The argument against nuclear power  is an emotional one.
決定不能感情用事
And you don't make decisions  based on emotion.
感情用事的決定  根本不是決定
Decisions based on emotion  aren't decisions at all.
是直覺
Instincts.
也同樣有價值
Which can be of value.
理性與非理性能互補
The rational and the irrational  complement each other.
分開的話就沒什麼力量了
Individually, they're far less powerful.
那麼副總統的事  你比較傾向哪一種？
And which category do your thoughts  on the Vice Presidency fall into?
聽到那首歌嗎？
You hear that song?
是畫眉鳥
It's a hermit thrush.
你看不到它
Can't see him.
「獨來獨往的畫眉鳥
"Solitary, the thrush,
「像隱士般靜靜藏匿著
"The hermit, withdrawn to himself,
「離群索居
"avoiding the settlements,
「獨自唱著歌」
"Sings by himself a song."
知道這首詩嗎？
Do you know the poem?
- 不知道  - 華特惠特曼寫的
-No, I don't.  -Walt Whitman.
描述林肯之死  它就在那邊某處
It's about the death of Abraham Lincoln.  He's over there, somewhere.
我知道那首詩  我們在山特諾時學過
Yes, I know the damn poem.  We studied it at the Sentinel.
我問教授  「為什麼要哀悼總統之死
I said to my professor,  "Why mourn the death of presidents,
「或是哀悼任何人？  死人又聽不見」
"or anyone for that matter?  The dead can't hear us."
他問我相不相信有天堂  我說不相信
And he asked if I believed in heaven.  I said no.
然後他問我  是不是對神沒有信心
And then he asked if I had no faith in God.
我說你問錯了
I said you have it wrong.
是神對我們沒有信心
It's God that has no faith in us.
深入森林吧
Deeper into the woods.
我覺得你有點偏執
I think you're being paranoid.
我一坐下來他就出現  太詭異了
He came up right after I sat down.  It was creepy.
我告訴你，是沃麥克
I'm telling you, it was Womack.
是安德沃說的嗎？
Is that what Underwood said?
他沒說名字，但還會是誰？
He didn't name names, but who else?
有什麼大不了的？  議員們總是互欠人情
And what's the big deal?  Congressmen trade favors.
有一個議員自殺了
One of these congressmen  committed suicide.
我覺得你想太多了，珍妮
I think you're stretching here, Janine.
- 試著聯想…  - 我曾經追過大新聞
-To try and connect...  -I have gone after big fish before.
我知道被監視的感覺
I know what it feels like to be watched.
安德沃的教育提案  在沃麥克成為多數黨領袖
Underwood's Education Bill went  to the floor just three days
三天後就獲得通過
after Womack became Majority Leader.
你先透露教育提案的事  接著是凱恩的社論
You leaked the Education Bill.  And then there was the Kern article.
這是兩個完全不同的報導…
Those were two  completely different stories...
等等，那傢伙是誰？  他叫什麼？
Wait, what was the guy?  What was his name?
就是叫凱恩  幫校刊寫社論的人？
He's the one who told that Kern wrote  the article for the school paper?
- 羅伊卡普奈  - 你應該去找他談
-Roy Kapeniak.  -You should go talk to him.
- 這之間沒關聯  - 你就是關聯
-There's no link.  -Except you.
安德沃一直在利用你，喬伊  你不想知道原因嗎？
Underwood's been using you, Zoe.  Don't you want to know why?
- 你好  - 瑞米丹頓在二線
-Hi.  -Remy Danton's on line two.
他說有要緊事
He says it's important.
- 你好，瑞米  - 你好，克萊兒
-Hello, Remy.  -Hey, Claire.
我接到善可工業公關部的電話
I got a call from the PR team at SanCorp.
他們說吉莉安柯爾不配合
They said Gillian Cole  isn't being cooperative.
還沒跟他們連絡嗎？
Hasn't gotten back to them, you mean?
不是，她直接說  不想要攝影小組過去
No, told them point blank  she doesn't want the film crew there.
我正在看電子郵件
I'm looking at an email.
她說他們會  「破壞計劃和當地社區」
She wrote that they would be "disruptive  to the project and local community. "
這是她還是你的意思？
Is that her, or is that coming from you?
我很清楚告訴她要配合他們
No, I made it very clear  that I wanted her to work with them.
看起來她做的事完全相反
Well, it seems like she's doing the opposite.
我會找她談
I will speak to her.
然後我會親自和公關部溝通
And then I'll sort things out with  the PR team personally.
- 謝謝，克萊兒  - 不客氣
-Thank you, Claire.  -You bet.
吉莉安在吃午飯嗎？
Is Gillian at lunch?
她還沒進來，她身體不舒服
She didn't come in yet today.  She's not feeling well.
等她進來跟我說
Let me know when she gets here.
- 你的飛機幾點？  - 6點40分
-What time is your flight?  -6:40.
我們得出發了，路上會塞車
We should get going.  There's gonna be traffic.
差不多好了
Almost ready.
我最近在想
I've been thinking,
你交往過的老男人  是不是安德沃？
the older man you were with,  was it Underwood?
所以這整件事是為了  掩蓋你自己的過去？
So what this is really about  is covering your own ass?
不是這樣
That is not true.
你不想讓人知道你和他上床
You don't want anybody  to know you were sleeping with him.
這樣報導就不客觀了吧？
Not exactly objective reporting, is it?
別教我什麼新聞道德
Don't fucking lecture me  on journalistic ethics.
你在《先軀報》有多少報導
How many of the stories  you brought me at The Herald
- 是因為你…  - 我不想繼續討論
-were because you were...  -I'm not gonna have this conversation.
你該叫計程車去機場
Fine. Maybe you should take  a cab to the airport.
- 別因為我的誠實懲罰我  - 你沒有誠實
-Don't punish me for being honest.  -You haven't been honest.
是我先問的  你還沒有給我直接的答案
I had to ask. And you still haven't  given me a straight answer.
對
Yes.
就是他
It was him.
- 我不能接受，喬伊  - 什麼？
-I don't know if I can do this, Zoe.  -Do what?
你為了往上爬和議員睡覺
You fucked a congressman to get ahead.
我又不是第一個  做這種事的人，盧卡斯
I'm not the first person  to ever do something like that, Lucas.
但我沒和那些人上床吧？
But I'm not sleeping  with those other people, am l?
你現在恨我了？
What, so you just hate me now?
我應該是愛你  這才是問題所在
No, I probably love you.  That's the fucking problem.
走吧，我車子亂停
Let's go, I'm parked illegally.
聽說你們今天去逛森林
So I hear you went stomping  through the woods today.
沒錯，瑞蒙還很好心  安排我參觀富爾頓核電廠
We did, and then Raymond was kind enough  to arrange a tour of the Fulton Plant.
你當時一定在想
I'm sure you were wondering,
「這老傢伙什麼時候  才要說重點？」
"When is this old fool gonna get around  to brass tacks?"
我只是來這裏回答問題的
I'm here to simply answer questions.
我覺得等你準備好了  自然會有個答案
I figured that you would make up your mind  when you're ready.
我們兩個要一起決定
There are two minds here.
我們知道盲目信託的事
We know all about the blind trust.
這會讓你們擔心嗎？
Does it concern either of you?
「盲目」和「信託」  不是我最喜歡的詞
The words "blind" and "trust" are not among  my favorites in the English language.
但原則上我沒意見
But I have no problem with it in theory.
可以幾年不用  親自管理我們的資產
Not managing our assets for a few years
會讓我們減輕許多壓力
could unburden us  from a great deal of stress.
那你們的不情願是來自哪裏？
Well, then what does your  reluctance stem from?
你覺得總統為什麼要選我？
Why do you think the President wants me?
雖然我不能代表他說話  但如果是我…
Well, I can't speak on his behalf,  but if I were to...
你不就是為了這個來的嗎？
Aren't you here to do just that?
代表他說話？
Speak on his behalf?
如果要我做推測  我認為總統會…
If I were to speculate,  I think the President would...
推測是很糟的投資方式  對政治來說也很糟
Speculation is a poor form of investment,  and an equally poor form of politics.
告訴我你知道什麼
Tell me what you know.
我不懂你的意思
I don't know what you mean.
你認為我該怎麼做？
Well, what do you think I should do?
以你法蘭安德沃的角度來說？
You personally, Frank Underwood?
- 我的意見不重要  - 對我來說很重要
-My opinion isn't what matters here.  -lt does to me.
我該接受嗎？該還不該？
Should I do it? Yes or no?
有很多事情要考慮，瑞蒙…
Well, there's a great number of things  to consider, Raymond...
我相信你早已考慮過了  法蘭，該還不該？
And I'm sure you've considered them all.  Yes or no, Frank?
- 我不會回答這個問題  - 因為你覺得我不該接受
-No, I will not answer that question.  -Because you think I shouldn't.
因為這沒有關聯性
Because it's not relevant.
那我換個方式問你
All right, then, let me ask you another way.
你會接受嗎？
Would you take the job?
我不是人選之一
It hasn't been offered to me.
如果你是呢？
What if it were?
我討厭做假設
I have a distaste for hypotheticals
就像你討厭推測一樣
just the same as you have  a distaste for speculation.
好吧
All right, all right.
今天談太多公事了  我們可以明天再說
That's enough business for now.  We can discuss it more tomorrow.
快進去，布魯斯
Get in there, Bruce.
抱歉打擾你了，女士  我在找羅伊卡普奈
Sorry. Sorry to bother you, ma'am.  I'm looking for Roy Kapeniak.
我以為他的拖車在附近  我有走錯嗎？
I thought his trailer was over here.  Am I in the right place?
一個月前是沒錯，他被軀逐了
You're in the right place a month ago.  He got evicted.
- 他在這裏亂開槍太多次  - 你知道哪裏能找到他嗎？
-Shooting off his gun too much in the yard.  -Do you know where I can find him?
要做什麼？
Why?
我是他親戚，他侄女
I'm a relative. His niece.
我聽說他進城了
Skipped town is what I heard.
有個女孩和他同居  或許她知道
Had a girl living with him. Maybe she knows.
- 她叫艾可  - 艾可？
-Name was Echo.  -Echo?
至少是她的藝名
What she went by, at least.
在40號那裏的脫衣酒吧工作
Works at the titty bar over on 40.
- 40號公路？  - 漢堡王對面
-Highway 40?  -Across from the Burger King.
好，謝謝
Okay. Thank you.
須年滿21歲  備有證件
女士免費入場
Girls get in free.
我在找艾可
I'm looking for Echo.
- 誰？  - 艾可？
-Who?  -Echo?
羅伊是瘋子  我頭腦壞了才會和他同居
Roy was a fucking wacko.  I was stupid to live with him as long as I did.
- 你知道他在哪裏嗎？  - 不知道也不關心
-Do you know where he is now?  -I don't know and I don't care.
- 他提過我寫的文章嗎？  - 說個不停，還裱框起來
-He ever talk about the article I wrote?  -All the time. He had it framed.
如果沒有被丟掉的話  就一定還在拖車裏
Bet it's still in the trailer,  if it's not in a junkyard by now.
他有跟你說  為什麼打電話給我嗎？
Did he say why he called me?  Did he ever tell you?
我人在現場
I was there.
- 在哪裏？  - 那個人出現的時候
-Where?  -When the guy showed up.
誰？
Who?
我不會指名道姓
I won't name names.
去他的羅伊卡普奈  你不欠他什麼
Fuck Roy Kapeniak. You don't owe him shit.
那個人說自己是議員
Some guy who said he was a congressman.
是他嗎？
Was it him?
不是，比較年輕
No, he was younger.
很高、頭髮不多、蠻帥的
Tall. Not much hair. Pretty good-looking.
就是他
Yeah, that was him.
你確定嗎？
You're absolutely sure?
他帶了波本威士忌和毒品  待了一整晚
He brought bourbon, blow,  stayed the whole night.
全都是他的主意
The whole thing was his idea.
說凱恩寫了那篇社論嗎？
What, to say that Kern wrote the editorial?
那傢伙沒寫過任何東西  都是羅伊寫的
That guy didn't write anything.  It was all Roy.
我說過我不會指名道姓
Okay, I know I said  that I wouldn't name names.
如果你不希望，我不會提  但你可以一夜成名
And I won't, if that's what you want.  But you could be famous overnight.
- 脫口秀，電視節目，全國…  - 不可能
-Talk shows, TV, the whole country...  -No way.
你就不必再跳舞了  想做什麼都可以…
You wouldn't have to dance anymore.  You could do whatever you want...
別提到我的名字  我已經說太多了
Don't use my fucking name, okay?  I already said more than I should have.
- 史坦普，已經半夜了  - 兩件事，老闆
-Stamper, it's midnight.  -Two things, boss.
首先，珍妮史柯斯基  今早突襲克裏絲汀娜
First, Janine Skorsky ambushed  Christina this morning.
我打斷她  以免她問太多問題
I intercepted her  before she could ask too much.
我們該擔心嗎？
Should we be worried?
我能搞定，長官  我只是想讓你知道
I can keep this contained, sir.  I just wanted you to know.
好，另一件事呢？
All right. What's the other thing?
多爾的調查結果出來了  我剛傳給你
Doyle came back with his research.  I just emailed it to you.
總統說他和塔斯克不太熟吧？
The President told you he  and Tusk didn't know each other, right?
對，他說他們只見過一次面  好像是在募款會
Yeah, he said they met once,  I think at a fundraiser.
那是謊話
That would appear to be a lie.
我打開了
All right, I have it in front of me now.
多爾列出所有他能找到
Doyle cataloged all  the instances he could find
他們倆同時出現  在同一城市的情形
in which the two of them were  in the same city at the same time.
標紅色的是  他們同時出席的活動
Items in red are events  that they both attended.
他還有其他發現
And he found something else.
沃克還在私營部門的時候  他是先鋒航空的總裁
Back in Walker's private sector days  he was the CEO of Pioneer Airlines.
被賣給聯合航空時  猜猜誰擁有三分之一股權？
Guess who owned a third of the stock  when it was sold to United?
瑞蒙塔斯克
Raymond Tusk.
我猜他和沃克很熟
My guess is that he and Walker  know each other quite well.
讓我看一下，晚點再打給你
All right, let me look this over.  I'll call you back.
我被耍了
I'm being played.
可是為什麼？
But why?
- 我又吵醒你了嗎？  - 沒有
-Did I wake you again?  -No.
我想跟你談談
I'd like to talk.
給我一分鐘
Give me a moment.
- 卡羅來納長尾鸚鵡  - 錯了，不過很接近
-Carolina Parakeet?  -You're wrong, but you're close.
這是太陽鸚哥
This is the Sun Conure.
它們長得很像  但卡羅來納長尾鸚鵡已經絕種
They look very similar,  but the Carolina Parakeet is extinct.
被殺光了  因為當時被認為是害蟲
Was killed off  because it was considered a pest.
但它們是種有趣的鳥
Interesting species, though.
特別貪吃
Voracious appetite.
它們有毒，貓吃了會死
And he was poison. Cats who ate him died.
這隻鳥不是你來聖路易後  唯一認錯的東西
This bird is not the only thing you've  misidentified since you've been in St. Louis.
你和沃克是老朋友  我不是被派來審查你的
You and Walker are old friends.  I wasn't sent here to vet you.
很好
Very good.
告訴我，我來這裏做什麼
Tell me why I am here, then.
讓我可以審查你
So I can vet you.
為了副總統的位子？
For the Vice Presidency?
總統很重視我的建議
The President values my advice,
而且會聽從
and he tends to follow it.
像是我曾建議他  別讓你當國務卿
Like when I advised him  not to make you Secretary of State.
- 那建議糟透了  - 的確是
-That was very bad advice.  -Yes, it was.
那是我犯過的重大錯誤之一  我很少犯錯
One of the larger mistakes I've made,  and I rarely make mistakes of any size.
你已經證明自己很難對付
You've proven yourself to be quite difficult.
凱恩、教師罷工  現在又有馬修…
Kern, the teachers' strike, now Matthews...
你把這些都算在我頭上？
You attribute all that to me?
這是我的猜測
If I had to guess.
有位智者曾告訴我  推測對政治來說是很糟的方式
A smart man once said to me that  speculation is a poor form of politics.
瑞蒙，何不說你知道的事情？
Why don't you stick  to what you know, Raymond?
我知道只要你下定決心  就能發揮高度效率
What I know is you are extremely effective  at what you set your mind to.
這對我非常有價值
That is valuable to me,
我已經告訴葛瑞  這對他會很有幫助
and I've already told Garrett  that it could be valuable to him.
在他的團隊裏  能有人一腳在行政部門
Somebody at his side  with one foot in the Executive Branch
一腳在立法部門
and one in the Legislative.
他對這想法持開放的態度
He is very open to the idea.
換我猜了
My turn to speculate.
你的推薦是有價錢的
Your recommendation comes at a price.
沒錯
Fact.
我有你需要的東西  你有我需要的東西
I have something that you want,  you have something that I want.
我說了什麼好笑的話嗎？
Have I said something amusing?
我談判時大多是坐在你那邊
I've just sat too many times  on your side of the table
現在發現自己坐在另一邊  覺得很諷刺
not to enjoy the irony of finding myself  on this side of it.
想聽聽我要的是什麼嗎？
Would you like to hear what I want?
我不會讓自己被陌生人束縛
I don't shackle myself to people I don't know.
我只想要一個人情
What I want is one favor.
只有一個
One and only one.
是什麼？
Which is?
在我冒險說出細節之前  我需要你先答應
I need to be certain you'll grant it before  I'll take the risk of being more specific.
- 一張空白支票  - 差不多
-A blank check.  -Of sorts.
你絕對不會開空白支票給別人
You would never grant anyone a blank check.
對
No.
但我現在不是坐在那一邊
But I'm not sitting on that side of the table.
在我家鄉  我們仍相信握手的誠信
We still believe in handshakes  where I come from.
在華府還流行嗎？  你要打給誰？
Do they still mean anything in Washington?  Who are you calling?
- 叫車送我去機場  - 法蘭
-Car service to get me to the airport.  -Frank.
我會告訴總統  我需要仔細考慮
I will tell the President  that I want until Friday
週五再給他我的建議
to think things over before  I make my recommendation.
如果你改變主意就通知我  讓我替你安排車子
Let me know ifyou change your mind.  And let me arrange the car for you.
你好，我想叫車
Hi, I'd like to arrange a car, please.
女廁
- 你還好嗎？  - 比昨天好
-How are you feeling?  -Better than yesterday.
不過如果又開始想吐  可能會早退
But I might take off early  if the nausea comes back.
我覺得很巧，你打發走  善可工業隔天就沒來上班
I find it interesting that you stay home the  day after you blow off the SanCorp people.
你不是不舒服，吉莉安
You weren't feeling sick, Gillian.
你指控我利用懷孕做藉口  這樣非常過分
I find it extremely offensive that you'd  accuse me of hiding behind my pregnancy.
你知道我要什麼
You knew what I wanted.
波札納計劃是我的
The Botswana project is mine.
在我的保護傘下  用我募來的資金
Under my umbrella. Using money I raised.
你答應讓我全權處理
You promised me autonomy.
麻煩迴避一下
Excuse us for a moment, please.
我答應讓你變強大
I promised to empower you.
這跟你不徵求我的意見  擅自行動是不一樣
That's not the same thing as you doing  as you choose without consulting me.
我不會允許  我花了三年時間的計劃…
I'm not going to allow a project  I've put almost three years of my life into...
如果沒有善可工業  你的計劃根本不會開始
Your project wouldn't be happening  if it weren't for SanCorp.
我沒要他們幫忙
I didn't ask for their help.
那你簽協議之前  先問問我的意見如何？
How about consulting me  before you struck a deal?
有件事你要搞清楚  這個組織是屬於我的
Let's get something very clear,  I run the organization.
你只是在這裏工作而已
You work for it.
我們的協議是一起聯手  克萊兒
Our agreement is an affiliation, Claire.
- 世安不是你的附屬品  - 它是
-WorldWell isn't your vassal.  -Yes, it is.
如果要說得這麼白  它完全是我的
Entirely. If we're going to be blunt about it.
這不是你六個月前的提議
That's not what you proposed  six months ago.
你的合約上是這麼寫的
It's what you signed up for  when you signed the contract.
我們有很好的信任關係  瞭解…
There was a good faith understanding that...
你違抗我  這種信任關係被破壞了
And you've dissolved that  good faith by disobeying me.
違抗你？
Disobeying you?
對
Yes.
我威脅到你了吧？
I threaten you, don't l?
你對我完全不構成威脅
Nothing about you threatens me.
但你也許該休假一陣子
But maybe you should  take a leave of absence.
你要開除我嗎？
Are you firing me?
隨你怎麼想  但你現在該離開了
That's up to you.  But right now, you should leave.
- 你有把她錄下來嗎？  - 沒有，她不會和我談
-Did you get her on record?  -No. She wouldn't talk to me otherwise.
我們需要確切的證據  來證明安德沃是幕後主謀
Well, we need hard proof  that Underwood was behind it.
這整件事讓我非常緊張
This whole thing  is making me really nervous.
怕你會曝光？
That you'll be exposed?
不是
Not that.
是法蘭斯
It's Francis.
如果內幕這麼複雜  他又早就在監視你…
If this really goes as deep as we think,  and he's already watching you...
你覺得他很危險？
You think he's dangerous?
我知道他很危險
I know he is.
所以我們才必須繼續
Then that's why we have to keep going.
他會把人摧毀，珍妮
He crushes people, Janine.
- 你好，卡倫  - 你好
-Hey, Callum.  -Hey.
聽著，如果你不害怕  就不會做這份工作
Look, if you weren't afraid,  you wouldn't be doing your job.
我寫過真正有價值的報導  都讓我嚇得半死
The only articles that I have ever written  that truly mattered scared the shit out of me.
我們需要知道  關於魯索的所有事
We need to know about anything  that might've happened with Russo.
安德沃能用來控制他的事
Something Underwood  could have held over him.
我們得回去  找克裏絲汀娜葛蘭格
We have to go back to Christina Gallagher,
- 看她能不能提供什麼線索  - 我不能去
-see if she'll give us something.  -lt can't be me.
- 如果我再回去…  - 我去
- If I go back for a second time...  -I'll do it.
你真的不知道  總統和塔斯克的關係密切？
You honestly had no idea that  the President and Tusk were close?
在競選過程中和當選後
He never showed up once  on any call sheet, phone log
他從未出現在電話簿  電話紀錄或行事歷上
or schedule during the campaign  or since we've been in office.
我很想相信你，琳達  但這有點困難
I'd love to believe you, Linda,  but I'm finding it very difficult.
我瞞著你有什麼好處？
What would I gain  by keeping you in the dark?
我和你一樣震驚，法蘭
I am as shocked as you are, Frank.
- 別表現出你知道的樣子  - 當然不會
-Well, don't let on that you know.  -Of course not.
總統怎麼說？
What's the President saying?
他想約你週二匯報  有關塔斯克的事
He wants to meet with you Tuesday  to get your report on Tusk.
真可笑
That's a farce.
要不要我找理由延期？
Should I come up with a reason  to delay the meeting?
不，也許能瞭解內情，幾點？
No, maybe we'll learn something. What time?
- 下午2點  - 我會到的，謝謝，琳達
-2:00 p.m.  -All right, I'll be there. Thank you, Linda.
我們還有一周
We have one week.
- 達到什麼目的？  - 找到塔斯克的弱點
-To accomplish what exactly?  -To force Tusk's hand.
他想要我欠他人情？不可能  我們得讓他爬著來求我
He wants me beholden to him? No.  We have to make him to come crawling to me.
他的弱點是什麼？
What's his weakness?
他的資產
His fortune.
- 那不是他的優點嗎？  - 如果開始減少就不是了
-Wouldn't you say that's his strength?  -Not if it's slipping away.
你要怎麼讓四百億  在一天內消失？
How do you make $40 billion  disappear overnight?
不行，但也許我們能製造  處於險境的假象
We can't, but maybe we can create  the illusion that it's in danger.
你給我他的那份資產簡報
The brief you gave me on his assets,
核能產業佔了多少？
how much of his total net worth  is in nuclear power?
大概三分之一
About a third.
國內有16座反應爐  國外有37座
Sixteen reactors here in the States,  37 worldwide.
這就是我們的目標  從他的核能收益下手
Well, that's what we hit him with.  We go after his nuclear interests.
就算如此，他的其他投資  還有250億…
Even so, he's got $25 billion  in other investments...
道格，他是白手起家的人
Doug, this is a man who built  his fortune from nothing.
錢對他來說不算什麼  重要的是背後代表的意義
The money doesn't mean anything to him.  It's what it represents.
什麼意義？
Which is what?
他畢生的努力
His life's work.
打給瑞米丹頓  盡快安排個會議
Get Remy Danton on the phone.  Set up a meeting as quickly as you can.
塔斯克瞭解  權力和金錢之間的差別
Tusk understands the difference  between power and money.
所以他是個危險人物
That's precisely what makes him dangerous.
他衡量財富的標準  不是私人飛機，而是收買靈魂
He doesn't measure his wealth  in private jets, but purchased souls.
我付出這麼多努力  眼看一伸手就能得到獎賞了
I've worked too hard  to get within arm's reach of the prize
我絕不會在得到之前  讓我的手砍掉的
only to have my hand cut off  just before I seize it.
我是喬伊邦斯  來見克裏絲汀娜葛蘭格
Zoe Barnes, here to see Christina Gallagher.
抱歉，沒有你的預約
I'm sorry, I don't see an appointment.
一定是搞錯了，我約了11點半
There must be a mistake. I have an 1 1:30.
請稍等
One second.
我叫喬伊邦斯，在《頭條報導》工作  你和我同事珍妮史柯斯基聊過
My name is Zoe Barnes, I work at Slugline.  You spoke to my colleague, Janine Skorsky.
- 小姐  - 我們沒事，謝謝
-Miss.  -We're fine, thanks.
你不能就這樣進來…
You can't just come in here...
彼得有些事是你不知道的
There are things you don't know about Peter.
- 我寫了羅伊卡普奈的報導…  - 請馬上離開
-I wrote the article about Roy Kapeniak...  -Please leave. Right now.
是彼得說服他來找我的
It was Peter who convinced him  to talk to me.
什麼？我不懂…他為什麼…
What? I don't understand... Why would he...
有人對他施壓
Somebody pressured him to do it.
他是1月24日晚上  去見卡普奈的
The night of January 24.  That's when he went to speak to Kapeniak.
你記得就職典禮前後  有什麼不對勁的事嗎？
Do you remember anything strange  around the time of the inauguration?
他有什麼可能的把柄嗎？
Anything that could have been  held over him?
我不記得
No, I don't.
如果他捲入某些事  導致他自殺
If he was mixed up in things that  in any way contributed to his suicide,
你不會想知道嗎？
wouldn't you want to know?
我不想帶給你更多痛苦
I'm not trying to cause you any more pain.
我只想知道真相
I just want the truth.
你比任何人更有權利知道
And you deserve that more than anyone.
- 哪一天？  - 1月24日
-What was the date?  -The 24th of January.